I'm Terry Haley, and this is my wife, Martha.
Hi. And we met Phil through an accident
and geez, we were treated like family.
We had a hit and run on my wife's car, and I stopped in
and talked to Ed and geez,
you would've thought that we'd known him forever.
And, uh, we were really taking care of.
He handled everything. It
Was perfect, and it was done well.
You couldn't fill it all. Nope.
And then we got a new car
and he bought our old car. Oh, I did.
Yeah. Yes. How long have you guys been married?
53 years. 53 years?
Yeah. Without a misunderstanding.
Without a, do you believe that?
What would you recommend people
who wanna stay married as long as you guys do?
What's your clue? Oh, my. Oh gosh. Let's see.
You have to be flexible, that's all.
You just have to be flexible, so you can't always be right,
but she is, of course. Yeah.
I'm always right. Behave yourself. I always do.
Keep an eye on him. Oh, I always,
and that will be in good shape.
Okay. Okay. Okay.